<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on William Hearn</title>
    <link>http://sylus.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on William Hearn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 22:00:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sylus.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resumé</title>
      <link>http://sylus.ca/resum%C3%A9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sylus.ca/resum%C3%A9/</guid>
      <description>Personal Highlights  GoC Cloud Native Working Group  Meetup Website GitHub Youtube  Open Source involvement:  Official Docker images (Drupal Alpine) Official Kubernetes Helm charts (Hadoop, NiFi, Kylo) Extensions to Azure ACS Engine (Chocolately)  Maintainer of Drupal WxT 7&amp;frasl;8  Drupal 7 WxT Drupal 8 WxT  Technical Architect:  Open Government Portal (Drupal 7&amp;frasl;8) Statistics Canada Portal (Drupal 7&amp;frasl;8)   Education Honors, Bachelor of Computer Science, Carleton University // Minor in Psychology // September 2006 – August 2010</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Windows Apps with Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://sylus.ca/blog/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 22:00:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sylus.ca/blog/windows/</guid>
      <description>Windows and Kubernetes Windows is reaching near parity with Linux in terms of its support for Kubernetes. Due to this we can support various types of Windows workloads in a container and consequently to run in Kubernetes cluster. During the course of this presentation, we&amp;rsquo;ll go over some of the key considerations such as handling secrets, required node selectors, and other common differences you may encounter in clusters with Windows &amp;amp; Linux nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AKS: Infrastructure as Code</title>
      <link>http://sylus.ca/blog/aks/iac/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 06:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sylus.ca/blog/aks/iac/</guid>
      <description>Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) is now general availability (GA) and with that announcement a slew of longstanding issues have been addressed! Most importantly you can now leverage a custom vnet and RBAC with your cluster. These were key blockers for many organizations fully going down the AKS route as opposed to ACS Engine where you still have the master node under your purview.
Notably the AKS workflow in the Azure portal has been noticably improved and for quick one-off installations I would recommend going that route.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>