<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on William Hearn</title><link>https://sylus.ca/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on William Hearn</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><atom:link href="https://sylus.ca/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://sylus.ca/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Elements</title><link>https://sylus.ca/elements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/elements/</guid><description>Table of Contents Heading 2 Heading 3 Heading 4 Heading 5 Emphasis Button Link Paragraph Ordered List Unordered List Notice Tab Accordions Code and Syntax Highlighting Blockquote Tables Image Gallery Slider Youtube video Custom video Here is an example of headings.</description></item><item><title>Hey, I am William Hearn!</title><link>https://sylus.ca/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/about/</guid><description>I am an Senior Cloud Architect / Open Source advocate currently working at Statistics Canada.</description></item><item><title>Page Not Found</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description>Hugoplate is a free starter template built with Hugo and TailwindCSS, providing everything you need to jumpstart your HTML project and save valuable time.</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://sylus.ca/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/resume/</guid><description>Table of Contents Highlights Open Source contributions on GitHub Senior Cloud Architect (IT-04) at Statistics Canada Senior Drupal Technical Architect (IT-03) at Statistics Canada Presentations Education Honors, Bachelor of Computer Science, Carleton University Game Development, Algonquin College Language Proficiency Security Clearance TECHNICAL SKILLS Work Statistics Canada [2019-11 to Present] Cloud Native Solutions Team [2018-06 to 2019-11] Enterprise Cloud Services Division [2011-06 to 2018-06] Web Content Management System Team Open Plus [2011-03 to Present] Technical Consultant Open Source [2013-09 to Present] Open Source Developer Awards Excellence in Service Delivery Award Employee Recognition Award Public Service Excellence Award Team of the Year Award GTEC Winner GTEC Honoree Merit Award A+ Certified Professional References Highlights Open Source contributions on GitHub canada-ca-terraform-modules Managed MySQL Flexible Server Managed PostgreSQL Flexible Server statcan Kubeflow Manifests Kubeflow Containers GateKeeper Policies Charts Argo Controller wxt Drupal WxT Composer Project for Drupal WxT Helm for Drupal WxT Senior Cloud Architect (IT-04) at Statistics Canada Managed diverse Kubernetes clusters across the entire Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) Currently 3+ years, including critical business workloads running on production clusters.</description></item></channel></rss>