<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on William Hearn</title><link>https://sylus.ca/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on William Hearn</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><atom:link href="https://sylus.ca/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://sylus.ca/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Elements</title><link>https://sylus.ca/elements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/elements/</guid><description>Table of Contents Heading 2 Heading 3 Heading 4 Heading 5 Emphasis Button Link Paragraph Ordered List Unordered List Notice Tab Accordions Code and Syntax Highlighting Blockquote Tables Image Gallery Slider Youtube video Custom video Here is an example of headings.</description></item><item><title>Hey, I am William Hearn!</title><link>https://sylus.ca/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/about/</guid><description>I am an Senior Cloud Architect / Open Source advocate currently working at Statistics Canada.</description></item><item><title>Page Not Found</title><link/><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description>Hugoplate is a free starter template built with Hugo and TailwindCSS, providing everything you need to jumpstart your HTML project and save valuable time.</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://sylus.ca/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sylus.ca/resume/</guid><description>Table of Contents Highlights Open Source contributions on GitHub (Current) Senior Technical Architect (IT-04) at Statistics Canada (Current) Senior Drupal Technical Architect (IT-03) at Statistics Canada (Previous) Presentations Education Language Proficiency Work Awards Public Service Excellence Award 2014 Team of the Year Award 2014 GTEC Winner 2014 GTEC Honoree 2013 A+ Certified Professional References Highlights Open Source contributions on GitHub (Current) canada-ca-terraform-modules Managed MySQL Flexible Server Managed PostgreSQL Flexible Server statcan Advanced Analytics Workspaces AAW Kubeflow Containers AAW Kubeflow Manifests GateKeeper Policies Charts wxt Drupal WxT Composer Project for Drupal WxT Helm for DrupalWxT Senior Technical Architect (IT-04) at Statistics Canada (Current) Senior Technical Architect (IT-04) of Cloud Native Team @ Statistics Canada Developed Concept of Operations for Kubernetes Cloud Native Platform used internally and shared with other departments Recieved Authority to Operate (ATO) for Kubernetes Cloud Native Platform through met Security Controls Recieved GCEARB approval for Kubernetes Cloud Native Platform Senior Drupal Technical Architect (IT-03) at Statistics Canada (Previous) Launched the Statistics Canada Website on Drupal Launched the Open Government Portal on Drupal Presentations Presented the Data Analytics as a Service Platform at Stratosphere 2020 PDF / YouTube Presented a two day course at the School of Public Service&amp;rsquo;s Digital Academy on Cloud Native technologies PDF / YouTube Education Honors, Bachelor of Computer Science, Carleton University // Minor in Psychology // September 2006 – August 2010</description></item></channel></rss>